（アランドロン）＜聖石矢魔学園へと
編入してきた→
Burying Punch!
Here are Oga and the gang having
entered into St. Ishiyama Academy.
男鹿たち一行。学園を影で統べる
六騎聖と対決するも→
Their showdown with the 6 Holy Knights who
secretly protect the school remains unfinished.
決着はつかないまま。→
舞台は次の場へと
持ち越されたのでございます＞
The arena has been postponed
to another place and time.
（東条）((待てよ！))
（男鹿）((逃げんのか？))
Hold it!
（三木）((叩きつぶす))
((ぬかせ))
You runnin' away?
I'll crush you.
（ベル坊）((デーッ！ダブー！))
Get lost.
（木戸）((１ヵ月後　本校で学園祭が行われる。→
In one month, we will hold a school festival.
そこで君たち７人と六騎聖の
決着の場を設けよう。→
There, you seven and the 6 Holy
Knights can finish things.
ただし　ケンカではなく
スポーツでだ))
But through sports, not fighting.
（チャイム）
（寧々）スポーツって　いったい
何させる気かしら。
Sports? I wonder what
they're gonna make us do?
（姫川）
大丈夫　大丈夫。要は何しても→
Don't worry. Whatever it
is, we just need to win.
勝ちゃいいんだからさ
なぁ　クイーン。
（邦枝）ちょっと黙ってて。
Right, Queen?
Just be quiet.
（古市）サッカーとか野球とかっすかね。
Soccer or maybe baseball?
（神崎）やったことねえぞ
そんなもん。
I ain't never done that crap.
（扉が開く音）
（佐渡原）はい　え～と→
U-Um... Please be quiet.
静かにして下さい。突然ですが
今日は転入生を紹介します。
I know this is a bit sudden, but I'd like
to introduce to you a new transfer student.
あ？
（佐渡原）君　入って。
Come on in.
アッ！
聖石矢魔への転校生なのだが→
She's a transfer student to St. Ishiyama,
本人の強い意向があって
このクラスに来ることになりました。
but due to her strong insistence,
she's come to this class.
え～　名前は…ヒル…。
H-Her name is... Hil...
（ヒルダ）ヒルデガルダです。
（佐渡原）これ　本名？
Hildegarde.
ヒルダとお呼び下さい。
Is that your real name?
Please call me "Hilda".
（男鹿・古市）ぬああ～っ！
アー！
よろしく。
It's my pleasure.
のおっ！
姐さあぁ～ん！
Madame Aoi!
What Has the Transfer Girl Done?
先生　私はどこに座ればよいのでしょうか？
Sensei, where shall I be seated?
あっ　好きなところに座りなさい
いっぱい空いてるでしょ。
Sit wherever you'd like. There're
plenty of empty seats, yes?
なるほど。
I see.
おい　貴様。
エエッ！？
Hey, trash.
どけ。
ええ～…。
Move it.
また変なのが来たよ！
We got another weirdo here!
ちょっと　あなた！
いきなり来て何言ってんのよ！
Hey, you! What are you doing
coming here like this?
空いてる席なら他にもあるでしょ！？
そっちに座りなさいよ！
There's plenty of other open seats, you know!
Go sit over there!
邦枝か…相変わらず勇ましいな。
Kunieda? Always the brave one, I see.
しかし私は　この方の
お世話をしなければならない。→
However, I must care for that one.
That one
席は近い方がいいだろう。
アーアッ！
It is best to have a seat nearby.
（真田兄）
おおっ！いきなり
女の戦いが始まったぞ！
And just like that, a catfight breaks out!
（真田弟）嫁対愛人かぁっ！？
The wife vs. the lover!
（涼子）姐さん　オレらが
ついてますよ！
（真田兄弟）いいぞ！やれやれ！
Madame, we'll back you up!
Get to it!
（古市）ちょっと待ったぁ～！！
Hold it right there!
何？
やめましょう。
こんな男鹿ハーレムみたいな展開。
What?
Stop this whole Oga harem
thing! It displeases me!
不愉快です。それに　ヒルダさんは
男鹿の嫁なんかじゃない。
And Hilda-san is not Oga's wife!
じゃ　何なんだ？
Then what is she?
言ってやれ！古市！
Say it, Furuichi!
妹です！
あ？
She's his little sister!
無理があんだろ～が！
んがぁ！
No one's gonna buy that!
ふむ　たまには悪くないものだな
学校というのも。
Sometimes this "school" thing is not so bad.
おい。
この制服というやつは
ちとキツイが。
Hey...
Although this "school uniform"
is a little tight...
てめぇ　一体何しに来やがった。
Why the hell did you come here?
つ～か　どうやって
転入してきたんだよ。
And how'd you transfer in anyway?
ふん　気になるか？
安心しろ　一個人として→
Curious?
Do not worry. I completed all the
necessary paperwork personally.
正規の手続きでやってきた。
今の私は　貴様の従妹で→
Right now I am posing as your cousin who has
transferred in from a respected private school.
名門私立からの転入生という
設定になっている。→
古市も　まんざら外してはおらん。
お～！
Furuichi was not entirely incorrect.
少々思うところがあってな。
I have my reasons...
それに　私だけではない。
アランドロンも来ておるぞ。
Plus, it's not just me.
Alaindelon is also here.
アランドロン？おっさんもか。
Alaindelon?
The big guy, too?
（アランドロン）((アイ　アム　ア　ペン))
《英語教師か何かか？》
I am a pen.
As an English teacher or something?
（先生）き　今日から　うちの
クラスの一員になる…。
He'll be a member of our
class starting today...
アランドロンです。
よろしくお願いいたします。
I'm Alaindelon! It's a
pleasure meeting you all.
（生徒たち）絶対　高校生じゃねえ！
There's no way he's in high school!
（廊下を走る音）
（由加）みんな！学園祭の競技が
決まったっス！
Everyone, the competition during the
school festival has been decided!
おう。
それで？
Oh?
And?
（涼子）はい。
バレーボールっス。
Right...
It's volleyball.
え？
Vol
Volleyball
（古市・男鹿）バレーボール。
Volleyball?
Halley's Comet
Volleyball
（姫川・東条・神崎）バレーボール。
Volleyball...
Black Hole
Volleyball
バレーボール！
Volleyball!
Big Bang
（一同）バレーボール！
Volleyball
Volleyball!
（三木）バレーボールで勝負って　どういう
ことですか！出馬さん！
What do you mean, compete
at volleyball, Izuma-san?
（出馬）うん？ちょうどええやろ
経験者もおらんし→
It's perfect, don't you think? No one has
any experience at it, and it's teams of 6.
人数的にもぴったりや
盛り上がるで。
This'll be fun.
ふざけないで下さい！
僕がつけたいのは→
Don't be ridiculous! The fight I want
to finish isn't a volleyball match!
そんな勝負じゃない！
っていうか　勝ったところで→
I don't think anyone will be
satisfied with that if we win!
誰も納得しませんよ！そんなの！
ほな　またケンカすんのか？
さすがに次は　かばいきれへんで。
What, gonna pick a fight again?
Next time I won't be able to cover for you.
だからって　何で…。
大丈夫　大丈夫。安心せえて。
Then why?
Don't worry about it! Relax.
ここだけの話　お前の決着の場も
ちゃんと用意しとんねん。→
This doesn't leave the room, but I've made
sure there's a place for you to finish things.
先生らにはナイショやけどな。
ほ　本当ですか？
The teachers don't know about it though.
R-Really?
フフフ…楽しくなるで！
This is gonna be fun!
あ…。
≪ファイト！≫
Fight! Fight! Fight!
（アランドロン）本当にいるんですかねぇ
こんな所に。
Is he really in a place like this?
わからん。
王宮の報告は当てにならんからな。
I don't know. The reports from
the palace are hit-and-miss.
だが事実だとすれば　大問題だ。
But if it's the truth, it's a big problem.
この学園に　我々の関与しない
悪魔が潜んでいるなどな。
We can't have an unrelated Demon
hiding here at this school...
とにかく油断するな。
尻尾を掴むまで→
Anyway, don't let your guard down. Until
we catch him, keep your eyes peeled.
気取られるなよ。
はい。
Yes, ma'am.
（ホイッスル）
全員集合！
Everyone, assemble!
アイ！
うっす！
Here!
これだけ？
男鹿が　そこで寝てます。
This is everyone?
Oga is sleeping over there.
コラッ！
うぐっ！
Hey!
（涼子）どうします？オレらだけ
練習しても意味ねえっすよ→
What'll we do? There's no
point for just us to practice.
退学組が来ねえと。
Not without the whole group up for expulsion.
（邦枝）
せっかく放課後１時間だけ→
And I went through the trouble to
reserve the gym after school too...
体育館貸してもらえるのに…
来てないのは？
Who isn't here?
（涼子）
神崎　姫川　東条　夏目っすね。
Kanzaki, Himekawa, Tojo...
And Natsume.
（邦枝）あいつら　退学になっても
いいのかしら。
Don't they care if they're expelled?
（由加）姐さん！こうなったら
色仕掛けっスよ！色仕掛け！
Madame Aoi! You should
bribe them with your body!
い　色仕掛け？
そうっスよ！ちゃんと練習に来て→
W-W-With my body?
That's right! We should say you'll show
them your boobs if they come practice!
試合に勝ったら
おっぱい見せるとか言うんスよ！
な…。
奴ら　これで鬼やる気出しますよ！
That'd totally motivate those idiots!
ウッ！
な・ん・で　姐さんがそんな→
And why should Madame Aoi have to
give that kind of fan service, huh?!
大サービスしなきゃ
いけないのよ！
は　入ってます　寧々さん…。
I-I give, Nene-san...
あんたが見せりゃ
いいでしょうが！
ウッ！
Why don't you show 'em yours instead, huh?
フッ…困っているようだな。
It looks like you're having issues.
おらっ　ウシチチ！
このタイミングで入ってくんな！→
Hey, cow-tits! This ain't
the time for butting in!
私らじゃ無理だとでも
言いたいんかい！
Are you sayin' that we ain't gonna cut it?
姐さんのスレンダーボディ　なめんなよ！
やめなさい。
Don't underestimate that
slender body of hers!
Please stop it.
ちょっと待ったあぁ～！
Hold it, everyone!
僭越ながら古市　流れに乗じて
言わせてもらいます！
ぜひ！
If I may presume, I'd like to say
something about this situation!
Please do!
色仕掛けというなら…→
If you're going to use sex appeal...
Everyone, please switch into bloomers!
全員ブルマ着用の方で
お願いします！
≪スリー　ツー　ワン…≫
ぐわぁ～！
（チーン…木魚の音）
アウ～。
さて　だいたいの事情はわかった。
バレーボールとやらで六騎聖と対決し→
Now then, I believe I
know the basic situation.
You'll play volleyball or something
with the 6 Holy Knights,
負けたら退学か…いいだろう。→
and if you lose you're expelled.
Great.
坊っちゃまも三木を倒したがって
おられる。
The Master also wishes to defeat Miki.
その役　私が買ってやろう。
I'll handle that part.
おいこら！男鹿嫁！
仕切ってんじゃねえよ！
っていうか何様！？
（涼子）
Hey, Oga's wife! You ain't our boss!
In fact, who are you?
何であんたに　そんなこと
決めらんなきゃなんないのよ！
What makes you think you can
just decide these things?
か　買うって　まさか　本当に…。
Play along? You don't mean...
フッ…要は　やる気を
出させればよいのだろう？
All I need to do is motivate them, yes?
（一同）エエッ！？
（夏目）フンフフフ～ン…。
フゥ～…。
うん？
ちょ…い…え…おお！？ああぁ～！！
おい。
あ？
Hey.
Huh?
なんだ　ここは？
Where are we?
っていうか　なんだ　この状況は！？
さっきまでオレ→
And why the hell are we tied up?!
I was just at home eatin' dinner!
家で晩飯食ってたよな？なあ！？
Right?
（姫川）オレが知るかよ。
How should I know?
I was watchin' TV, and then
suddenly this big dude appeared...
テレビ見てたら　いきなり目の前に
でかいおっさんが現れて…。
気がついたらこの状態だ。
お前もか。それってヒゲの？
Before I realized it, I was here like this.
You too? And he had a mustache?
ああ　しかも気のせえか
割れたような。
Yeah... And it might be me imagining
it, but I think he split open...
どうやらオレたち
拉致られたようだね。
It seems we have been abducted.
（神崎）夏目！
ってなんだ　その格好！
Natsume!
What the hell are you wearing?
風呂に入ってたら
タオルだけ巻かせくれた。
I was in the bath... All he
let me take was a towel...
教育的配慮だって。湯冷めしちゃう。
He said it was a special consideration...
I'm feeling chilled...
そんなのまだマシっすよ。
オレなんか　トイレにいる所を→
If only that were me!
I was taken while I was on the toilet!
連れてこられたんすよ。
もう　尊厳とかねえっすよ→
There's nothing left of my dignity!
あっ　全身は画面に
入れないで下さい。
フルチン…。
Please, don't put my entire body in frame...
Furuichi...
そこに東条さんもいますよ。
寝てますけど。
Tojo-san is over there, too.
He's sleeping though.
グア～…。
チッ　大物ぶりやがって。
And he's supposed to be the big boss...
要するに　退学組が
集められたってわけか。
So basically, all the people
being expelled are here.
男鹿はどうした！男鹿は！
What about Oga, huh?
ああ　男鹿ならそこに…。
Oh, Oga's over there.
ア！ウ！アイ！
（神崎）いったい何が！？
What in the world...
全員集まったようだな。
では　本題に入るとしよう。
It looks like everyone's here.
Now then, let's get on with the main affair.
男鹿嫁！てめえの仕業か！
このやろう！
Oga's wife, did you do this?!
そういや　あのおっさんも
見たことあんぞ！
Oh, yeah! I seen that big guy before!
どういうつもりだ　こらっ！
下　履かせて！
What the hell's the meaning of this?
Please let me put on some pants...
さっさと帰らせろや　ブスッ！
Let us go home this instant, you hag!
（ドガッ！ドガッ！ドガッ…！）
騒ぐな。私はただの使いだ。
Hush. I am simply assisting.
貴様らを集めた　あるお方のな。
Helping a certain master of
mine who has gathered you all.
《エッ！？あるお方って…
おいおい　まさか　大魔王！？》
A certain master?
Wait, don't tell me... The Great Demon King?
このディスクに　そのお方の
お言葉が入っている。→
This person has left a message
for you on this disk.
まずはそれを見てもらおうか。
First, have a look.
あ　それプロジェクターなんだ。
Oh... That was a projector...
《ええ～！？いやいやいや
マジか！？映ってんのか！？→
W-Wait, no way... He's on film?! The
Great Demon King finally shows up!
ついに大魔王登場？
こんなふざけたイベントで！？》
And for this completely stupid plot point?!
ハッ！
ようこそ諸君　私の名は…→
Welcome, comrades. My name is...
私の名は…私の名は！え～と…。
My name is...
My name is...!
Uh...
Bathim de Emuna Alaindelon
Welcome, comrades.
ようこそ諸君。私の名は…。
My name is...
Ｍｒ．バレーボール！
Mister Volleyball.
You're the old dude from before!
（夏目・姫川・古市）
さっきの　おっさんじゃねえかっ！！
Why are you talking through a monitor?
なんでモニター越し！？
黒幕気取りか！！
You think you could hide from us?
てゆ～か　横のマスコットも
かなり怪しいぞ。
無駄に高解像度！
And something's seriously wrong
with that mascot by your side!
You even went for full blown HD!
Just talk to us in person, damn it!
直接来い　直接！
何この茶番！！
What's with this farce?!
Mr. Volleyball worked to spread volleyball
far and wide during the war and...
Ｍｒ．バレーボールは　戦時下より
バレーボールの普及に努め→
その功績を…。（夏目）いいよ　そんな設定！→
We don't give a crap about the back story!
湯冷めしちゃうから
早く用件だけ言って！
I'm really getting chilled here,
so get to the point already!
Your left hand is only for support!
左手は添えるだけ。
（古市）バスケットボールだ　それは！！
That's basketball!
Is this some sort of prank! I'll kill you!
（姫川）
おちょくってんのか　てめ～！
マジ殺すぞ！！
ふふふ…いいね。
その若さ。負けん気。
I like that youth, that fierce spirit...
There can be no other reason
I've gathered you all.
そんな君達を集めたのは
他でもない。
ある映像を見てもらうためだ。
It was to show you this certain video.
映像？ふふふ…。
Video?
The V for Volleyball is the V for Victory!
バレーボールのＶは
ヴィクトリーのＶ！！
Now, start!
では　スタート！
（姫川）何だ　ここ？
Where is this?
This is the place where the 6 Holy
Knights are practicing in secret.
（Ｍｒ．バレーボール）
ここは　六騎聖が　秘密の特訓を
している場所だ。→
Well, just have a look.
まあ　見たまえ。
They're playing the
university volleyball team.
（Ｍｒ．バレーボール）
相手チームは　大学生バレー部。→
It seems like they were no match for
the St. Ishiyama volleyball team.
聖石矢魔のバレー部では
相手にならなかったらしい。
（Ｍｒ．バレーボール）どうだね？少しは
やる気になったか？
So? Does that motivate you a little bit?
Hey, hold it... Weren't they beginners?
おいおいおい。
こいつら素人じゃね～だろ。
Did you see those boobs?
見ました？あの胸。
胸かよ。
The boobs?
They were really jiggling...
超　揺れてたな。
じゃなくてこれマズイんじゃない。
Not that... We're in trouble, aren't we?
Don't you think the duck's
ass on specs is way too long?
小声
（アランドロンのアテレコ）
メガネ　リーゼント…長くね？
ん？おい待て　おっさん！→
Hey, hold it, old man!
Up the volume and play that video again!
今んとこ音量あげてもっかい流せ！
ん？ああ　かまわんよ。
Sure, I don't mind.
What?
何？
黙って聞いてろ。
Stay quiet and listen.
（アランドロン：静のアテレコ）
てゆ～か　あのリーゼント
超キモイんですけど～。
And like, yeah... That duck's
ass is totally gross!
Totally... And he's so lame too...
（アランドロン：三木のアテレコ）
ですよね～。しかも　姑息ですし→
I bet he slips his opponents laxatives...
下剤とか使ってきそ～。
な…。
Yeah, totally! Cowardly
or like, bush league!
（アランドロン：静のアテレコ）
あるある～！
卑怯（ひきょう）ってゆ～かちっさ～い。
There's no way they'll seriously practice.
（アランドロン：三木のアテレコ）
練習する気合もないですよ　絶対。
Yeah, but if that one with long hair
gets serious, he'll be real annoying.
（アランドロン：郷のアテレコ）
それなら　あのロン毛も
本気出すとか　相当ウザイぜ！
There was an idiot named Kanzaki,
but I forgot what he looks like.
（アランドロン：榊のアテレコ）
神崎とかいうバカもいたけど
どんな顔か忘れた萌え…ない。
はあ？
（アランドロン：出馬のアテレコ）待て待て君ら。
Wait, wait... You may say that, but
the Tojo guy smells like gutter trash!
そんなことゆ～たら　東条とか
ゆ～奴は　ドブの臭いがしたぜ！
（アランドロン：アレックスのアテレコ）
ハア…ハア…。だった～ら
男鹿と赤ん坊はうんこ臭いでした。
Still, Oga and that baby smell like shit!
《これ　完全にアテレコじゃん。
こんなの乗せられ…ん？》
That's so obviously dubbed over...
There's no way they'll buy...
ほ～う。
ガルル…。
They're buying it big time!
（古市）すげ～乗せられてる！！
おもしれ～じゃね～か。
ンマー！
This just got interesting...
（一同）え？
おっしゃ～！
（姫川）古市！
レシーブ上がったぞ！！
Take this!
Furuichi, set up the receive!
Leave it to me!
まかせろ！
こっちだ古市！
Over here, Furuichi!
Oh, no! Over here!
い～や　こっちだね。
Yo, it's me!
いや　オレだぁ～！
Yeah!
よっしゃあ～！！
っしゃあ～！！
ん？遅えぞ　邦枝！！
You're late, Kunieda!
…うそ。
No way...
ふっ。
（東条）声出せ～おらぁ～っ！！
Louder, you pieces of crap!
っしゃあ　おらぁ～っ！！
ま　まあ　とにかく→
Well as long as everyone's
excited about it...
みんなやる気になって
良かったじゃないすか？
うん。
Yeah...
Anyway, your duck's ass
is gettin' in the way!
（神崎）
てゆ～か　てめえのリーゼントが
邪魔だっつってんだろっ！！
Huh? This is my policy!
あぁ！？こいつはオレのポリシーだ。
文句あんのかっ！！
You got a problem with it?
Yeah I got a problem!
あんに決まってんだろ！
さっきからブロックの度に→
That damn chikuwa tube just got stuck
in the net when you went to block!
ネットに突き刺さってんだよ！
そのちくわぶが！！→
面白すぎんだよ！切れ　ボケ！
It's just amusing!
Cut it off, dolt!
あぁん！？
（邦枝）ちょ　ちょっとアンタ達…。
C-Come on, you two...
Kunieda, you tell him too!
邦枝　お前からも言ってやれ！
「それでどんなレシーブするの？
ぷっ…」とか。
Tell 'em like "how do you expect
to receive like that, heh"?
Die! I'm gonna friggin' kill you!
（姫川）しね～よ！
てめえ　マジぶっ殺すぞ！→
And what the hell you mean, chikuwa tube?!
だいたい　ちくわぶって何だよ！
え？
Late! Your reaction to "chikuwa
tube" is way too late!
（神崎）おっそ～！
ちくわぶ　反応おっそ！！
まあ　確かに　スポーツをやる
格好じゃないと思うけど…。
Well, true... It's not a very
appropriate outfit for sports...
Take a look!
ほら　見ろ。
フン！チッ。
Hold it! Where do you think you're going?
（邦枝）
あ　ちょっと　どこ行くのよ！
Let him go. We just need 6 people...
ほっとけよ。
ど～せ　６人いりゃいいんだ。
And he was obviously just holding us back...
正直あいつ足引っ張ってたしな～。
神崎！
Kanzaki!
せっかく　まとまりかけたと
思ってたのに…。
And I thought we'd finally gotten
everyone to take it seriously...
うん。
（由加）ひっめっかっわ先輩！
Himekawa-senpai!
Oh? What do you two want?
（姫川）あぁ？なんだ　てめ～ら。
Let's...
髪…。
下ろしましょう。
なっ…。
...let down your hair.
You've gotta be kiddin' me, you...
（姫川）
こら　ふざけんな　てめ～ら！
We're not kiddin'. We're
like, totally for reals.
ふざけてませんよ～マジ本気っス。
We ain't gonna let anyone
drag Madame Aoi down...
姐さんの足引っ張る奴は
オレら　許しませんからっ！！
（姫川）ひっ…うわぁ～！！
（一同）うわぁ～。
What are you staring at?
Let's get practice started.
何じろじろ見てんだよ。
さっさと練習始めっぞ。
No, uh...
（邦枝）いや　え…？
（寧々）どちら様？
Who might you be?
It's me, Himekawa.
姫川だよ　姫川。
みんなの姫川さんだよ！
I'm the Himekawa-san you know and love!
Can't you tell by looking at me?!
見りゃわかんだろ～が！！
No, we think you look like a
completely different person.
（一同）
いや…完全に別人じゃないですか。
え～っと　おほん。
じゃあ　全員そろったところで→
Um...
While we have everyone together,
let's decide on the positions.
ポジション決めましょう。
We need to take best advantage
of everyone's strengths to win.
（古市）
勝つためには　それぞれ
特性をいかさないと。例えばほら→
Like, see, there's a position
whose main job is receiving.
レシーブ専門のポジションとか
あるんすよ。知ってました？
Did you know?
Huh, what's that?
あ？なんだそりゃ？
オレはやだぞ。そんなポジション。
I don't like that sort of position.
The libero, yes?
リベロだろ？
制限は多いが　後衛の選手とも→
There's many restrictions,
but they can sub for the back-row players
anytime they want... A defensive specialist.
何度でも交代できる
守備専門の選手だ。
The color of their uniform
is also slightly different.
ユニフォームの色も
１人だけ違うし。
Something similar to the team's pivot...
ま　チームの要的存在だな。
Team's... pivot?
《チームの…》
《要…》
Hey, isn't that like a
team captain or something?
おい　それは
キャプテン的なあれか？
Then I'll do it.
だったらオレが。
いやいやオレが。
No, I'll do it.
No, I will...
いやいやオレが。
いやいや。
No...
But the libero isn't the captain.
いや　だから
リベロはキャプテンじゃね～って。
Me!
（邦枝）私よ！
（神崎・男鹿）あん？
ニョ？
I'll be the libero.
リベロは私がやる。アンタたち→
You people don't understand anything, right?
ど～せ何もわかってないんでしょ。
Come on, Kunieda. I didn't
think you'd be so picky.
おいおい　邦枝。
てめ～も案外せこいな。
そんなにキャプテンに
なりて～のか？
You really wanna be captain that bad?
That's not it, idiot.
（邦枝）違うわよ　バカ。
だから　リベロは…。
I'm trying to tell you, the libero isn't...
Furuichi.
古市！
へぶっ！！
私が決めてやろう。
（古市）あっああ…。
I will decide.
乗りかかった船だ。
とことん付き合うぞ。
There's no going back now. Come play with me.
（神崎）な　何だ　今の殺人サーブ！！
That serve could kill!
Whoa, the ball exploded!
（姫川）おいおいおい
ボールが破裂したぜ。
私のサーブを拾えたものがリベロ。
それでどうだ？
Whoever can return my serve is the libero.
How about that?
あ…。
ん…。
あ？
Fine.
（邦枝）いいわ。
姐さん！！
Madame Aoi!
来なさい。
ほう　お前がやるのか。面白い。
Get on with it.
Oh? You'll do it?
Interesting.
おおっ。
ジャンプサーブ！
A jump serve!
あ…。
（千秋・寧々）あ…。（夏目・神崎）あ…。
終りか？
Over already?
《は　速いなんてもんじゃない。
全く見えなかった…》
That wasn't just fast...
I couldn't see it at all!
うお～っ　なんつ～サーブだ。
That serve was nuts!
It buried itself into the wall!
壁にめり込んでんぞ！
There's no way a human could do that!
つ～か　人間業じゃね～だろ！
Well, she ain't a human...
あ～まあ人間じゃね～し。
Could you see her panties just now?
（古市）
今　パンツ見えませんでした！？
あ…あんなの
取れるわけね～っスよ。
There's no way to return that!
You could see her panties, right?
ねえ！パンツ見えましたよね！
寝てろ。
Go to sleep.
（邦枝）もう１本よ。
One more!
もう１本　お願いします。
Please, serve to me again.
よかろう。
As you wish.
《打たれたボールを
目で追ってちゃ間に合わない。→
Seeing the ball's path with
my eyes will be too late.
The crucial thing is the timing and
predicting its path the instant she shoots!
大事なのは　打つ瞬間の軌道予測と
タイミング！！》
Nene!
（邦枝）寧々！
は　はい！！
Yes?
ゴム貸して。
Let me borrow your hair tie.
あっ…。
ありがとう。
Thank you.
Moe...
萌え。
Next is sound, presence,
the flow of the air...
《あとは音・気配・空気の流れ》
Here I go.
いくぞ。
Sense them with my skin...
《それを　肌で感じること》
Look at that! Oga's wife jumped
twice as high this time!
あ…。
見ろ！男鹿嫁
さっきの倍は飛んでるぞ！
I do this all the time!
《いつもやっていることよ！！》
フッ！！
あっ！
（姫川・古市）な…。
S-She returned it!
（神崎）か　返した～っ！
And she did it right up against the net!
（姫川）
しかも　ネット前ドンピシャだぜ！
Chills up my spine, Madame Aoi!
姐さん！オニしびれたっス！
やりましたね！！
You did it!
（夏目）さて　そろそろ
練習再開といきますか。
Now then, shall we restart practice?
あっ。
What're you doing? Let's get started.
何してんだ　さっさと入れよ。
Guess we'll let you be captain.
しょ～がねえから　キャプテンは
てめ～に譲ってやらぁ。
ダ～ブ！
リベロな。
Libero.
Well, I was always more suited for spiking.
ま　オレはもともと
スパイク専門だしな。
By the way, Kunieda-senpai...
Are your arms okay?
てゆ～か邦枝先輩
腕とか大丈夫っすか？
待ちくたびれたぜ。
あ…あ？
I've gotten tired of waiting.
ということだ。
貴様がリベロでキャプテンだ。
There you have it.
You are the libero and captain.
All in one person.
しっかりまとめるんだな。
《この人　まさか
はじめから　このつもりで…》
She... Did she plan on this from the start?
っしゃあ～！！
いくぞ～！！
Here we go!
なんか…
いい感じになってきたっスね。
This is lookin' pretty good, actually...
（碇）待ちなっ！→
Wait!
You weren't the only ones
beaten by the 6 Holy Knights!
六騎聖を倒して～のは
てめ～らだけじゃね～ぜ。→
ＭＫ５＋１！
MK-5 + 1!
They show up, now?
このタイミングで出てくるか？
Look at 'em! They've got matching uniforms!
見てください！おそろいの
ユニフォームっスよ！！→
They're experts at pissin' me off!
腹立たしさが　パねえっ！！
（碇）聞いたぜ。
バレーボール対決だろ？→
We heard it's a volleyball match.
In that case, we'd be far more suited!
だったら　オレたちの方が
適任だぜ！勝負しろ！！→
Let's have a game!
勝った方が六騎聖と対決する！→
The winner gets to play the 6 Holy Knights.
今日のオレたちが
いつもの出オチだと思うかぁ！？
Do you really think we'll end
up today like the usual gag?
お！
も！
Yes!
Actually!
い！
ま～す！
We!
Do!
（ＭＫ５＋下川）ダメだこりゃ～！！
MK-5 + Shimokawa = Instant Loss
≪よっしゃ～！！≫
≪ヤッター！！≫
《なんだかんだ言って　運動神経は
いいのよね　あいつら》
Well, at least they're all athletic.
《いけるわ！》
We can do this!
（ドッド　ドドドド…）
え～いっ！！
ハア…ハア…。
Just a little longer...
（三木）あと　少し…。
For a man, sometimes you may know you
will lose, but still you must fight!
What are you saying that all
cool like for, Furuichi?
And sometimes you have to set up the
jokes, even though you know they'll bomb!
Don't go making rationalizations!
Anyway, make sure not to bomb there.
On the next Beelzebub: There
Are Wounds in the Past.
Okay then, set me up for one!
Did you say that a friend
had wounds in his past?
Do you think a kick would heel him?
And the joke is?
Uh...